流れてく　時の中ででも
Ever on and on I continue circling
気だるさが　ほらグルグル廻って
With nothing but my hate in a carousel of agony
私から　離れる心も
Till slowly I forget and my heart starts vanishing
見えないわ　そう知らない？
And suddenly I see that I can't break free — I'm
自分から　動くこともなく
Slipping through the cracks of a dark eternity
時の隙間に　流され続けて
With nothing but my pain and the paralyzing agony
知らないわ　周りのことなど
To tell me who I am, who I was — Uncertainty
私は私　それだけ
Enveloping my mind till I can't break free — And
夢見てる？　なにも見てない？
Maybe it's a dream; maybe nothing else is real
語るも無駄な　自分の言葉？
But it wouldn't mean a thing if I told you how I feel
悲しむなんて　疲れるだけよ
So I'm tired of all the pain, all the misery inside
何も感じず　過ごせばいいの
And I wish that I could live feeling nothing but the night
戸惑う言葉　与えられても
You can tell me what to say; you can tell me where to go
自分の心　ただ上の空
But I doubt that I would care, and my heart would never know
もし私から　動くのならば
If I make another move there'll be no more turning back
すべて変えるのなら　黒にする
Because everything will change and it all will fade to black
こんな自分に　未来はあるの？
Will tomorrow ever come? Will I make it through the night?
こんな世界に　私はいるの？
Will there ever be a place for the broken in the light?
今切ないの？　今悲しいの？
Am I hurting? Am I sad? Should I stay, or should I go?
自分の事も　わからないまま
I've forgotten how to tell. Did I ever even know?
歩むことさえ　疲れるだけよ
Can I take another step? I've done everything I can
人のことなど　知りもしないわ
All the people that I see I will never understand
こんな私も　変われるのなら
If I find a way to change, if I step into the light
もし変われるのなら　白になる？
Then I'll never be the same and it all would fade to white
流れてく　時の中ででも
Ever on and on I continue circling
気だるさがほら　グルグル廻って
With nothing but my hate in a carousel of agony
私から　離れる心も
Till slowly I forget and my heart starts vanishing
見えないわそう　知らない？
And suddenly I see that I can't break free — I'm
自分から　動くこともなく
Slipping through the cracks of a dark eternity
時の隙間に　流され続けて
With nothing but my pain and the paralyzing agony
知らないわ　周りのことなど
To tell me who I am, who I was — Uncertainty
私は私　それだけ
Enveloping my mind till I can't break free — And
夢見てる？　なにも見てない？
Maybe it's a dream; maybe nothing else is real
語るも無駄な　自分の言葉？
But it wouldn't mean a thing if I told you how I feel
悲しむなんて　疲れるだけよ
So I'm tired of all the pain, all the misery inside
何も感じず　過ごせばいいの
And I wish that I could live feeling nothing but the night
戸惑う言葉　与えられても
You can tell me what to say; you can tell me where to go
自分の心　ただ上の空
But I doubt that I would care, and my heart would never know
もし私から　動くのならば
If I make another move there'll be no more turning back
すべて変えるのなら　黒にする
Because everything will change and it all will fade to black
動くのならば　動くのならば
If I make another move, if I take another step
すべて壊すわ　すべて壊すわ
Then it all would fall apart. There'd be nothing of me left
悲しむならば　悲しむならば
If I'm crying in the wind, if I'm crying in the night
私の心　白く変われる？
Will there ever be a way? Will my heart return to white?
貴方の事も　私のことも
Can you tell me who you are? Can you tell me where I am?
全ての事も　まだ知らないの
I've forgotten how too see; I've forgotten if I can
重い目蓋を　開けたのならば
If I opened up my eyes there'd be no more going back
すべて壊すのなら　黒になれ！！！
'Cause I'd throw it all away and it all would fade to black!!!
badapple.priyavkaneria.com